<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Qingle Guo</title>
    <link>http://qingleguo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Qingle Guo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:27:21 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://qingleguo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Conference</title>
      <link>http://qingleguo.github.io/publications/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://qingleguo.github.io/publications/blog1/</guid>
      <description>Fusion of Hyperspectral and Lidar Data Based On Dual-Branch Convolutional Neural Network
Jinzhe Wang, Junping Zhang,Qingle Guo, Tong Li. 2019 IEEE International Geoscience and Remote Sensing Symposium, 2019
PDF
Change Detection for High Resolution Remote Sensing Image Based on Co-saliency Strategy
Qingle Guo, Junping Zhang. 2019 10th International Workshop on the Analysis of Multitemporal Remote Sensing Images, 2019
PDF
Change Detection for Mutil-Temporal Remote Sensing Images Based on NSCT and Hierarchical Clustering</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Degree</title>
      <link>http://qingleguo.github.io/blogs/ph.d-degree/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://qingleguo.github.io/blogs/ph.d-degree/</guid>
      <description>2018-Now Ph.D in Information and Communication Engineering Harbin Institute of Technology Major in Multitemporal Image Processing, Machine learning, Deep Learning and Remote Sensing. Proficiency and understanding in
 Image Processing algorithms Pattern recognition, Statistic learning and optimization methods C++, Python and Matlab Programming language Office, ENVI and Arcgis wroking software  2016-2018 M.S. in Information and Communication Engineering Harbin Institute of Technology Major in Change detection and Machine learning. Proficiency and understanding in</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience</title>
      <link>http://qingleguo.github.io/experience/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://qingleguo.github.io/experience/blog1/</guid>
      <description>2012-Now Obtained scholarship many times
 National Scholarship for Ph.D National Scholarship for M.S National People&amp;rsquo;s Scholarship for B.S  2016-Now Participant Many Scientific Researches including nations, company and regions.
 Algorithm and model design Writing materials and documents Acceptance and defense Coordination and Cooperation  2019-2020 Served as the secretary of SPIE Harbin Chapter and Reviewer of IEEE
 Organizing acitivities and communicating with other experts Reviewing the science papers Participanting and speeching in conference  2017-2019 Served as a Teaching Assistant for Signals and Systems</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal</title>
      <link>http://qingleguo.github.io/publications/blog2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://qingleguo.github.io/publications/blog2/</guid>
      <description>Deep Multiscale Siamese Network with Parallel Convolutional Structure and Self-Attention for Change Detection
Qingle Guo, Junping Zhang, Ye Zhang. IEEE Transactions on Geoscience and Remote Sensing, In press.(IF = 5.6 Top Journal)
[MSPSNet](Public soon)
Multiscale Semantic Guidance Network for Object Detection in VHR Remote Sensing Images
Shengyu Zhu, Junping Zhang, Xuejian Liang, Qingle Guo. IEEE Geoscience and Remote Sensing Letters, Jun. 2021.(IF = 3.966)
PDF
Change Detection for Hyperspectral Images Via Convolutional Sparse Analysis and Temporal Spectral Unmixing</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
